[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["earlier today"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJR", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "And on this particular point, Pamela, about the aggravated murder, which may well relate to him effectively forcing Michele Knight by starving her, and then beating her, to have repeated miscarriages, that is a pretty significant charge, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "on", "this", "particular", "point", ",", "Pamela", ",", "about", "the", "aggravated", "murder", ",", "which", "may", "well", "relate", "to", "him", "effectively", "forcing", "Michele", "Knight", "by", "starving", "her", ",", "and", "then", "beating", "her", ",", "to", "have", "repeated", "miscarriages", ",", "that", "is", "a", "pretty", "significant", "charge", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "It is, and we heard from the prosecutor earlier today saying that they are certainly going to look into that to see what the capability is for that.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", ",", "and", "we", "heard", "from", "the", "prosecutor", "earlier", "today", "saying", "that", "they", "are", "certainly", "going", "to", "look", "into", "that", "to", "see", "what", "the", "capability", "is", "for", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Knight"], "LOCATION": ["Pamela"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "WRB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "How he's faring now that obviously the game is up and he is the one in chains and he is the one facing a pretty horrendous time?", "question_tokens": ["How", "he", "'s", "faring", "now", "that", "obviously", "the", "game", "is", "up", "and", "he", "is", "the", "one", "in", "chains", "and", "he", "is", "the", "one", "facing", "a", "pretty", "horrendous", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, it all comes down to how much of this you believe is real and how much of it you believe is just him maybe faking it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "all", "comes", "down", "to", "how", "much", "of", "this", "you", "believe", "is", "real", "and", "how", "much", "of", "it", "you", "believe", "is", "just", "him", "maybe", "faking", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What can you tell me about that from your sources?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "that", "from", "your", "sources", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, one thing I just learned that's very eerie is all of the girls were kidnapped from the same general area.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "thing", "I", "just", "learned", "that", "'s", "very", "eerie", "is", "all", "of", "the", "girls", "were", "kidnapped", "from", "the", "same", "general", "area", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "But the belief from police, Ed, finally, is that all three women were lured into his car in different locations and then taken back to his house?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "belief", "from", "police", ",", "Ed", ",", "finally", ",", "is", "that", "all", "three", "women", "were", "lured", "into", "his", "car", "in", "different", "locations", "and", "then", "taken", "back", "to", "his", "house", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Was he in person more agitated?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "in", "person", "more", "agitated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "JJR", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Well, actually, he was arrestable.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "he", "was", "arrestable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Do you think if you had arrested him potentially you could have got into that house and found out what he was doing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "if", "you", "had", "arrested", "him", "potentially", "you", "could", "have", "got", "into", "that", "house", "and", "found", "out", "what", "he", "was", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I reflected on this many times since Monday, and actually, if I had arrested him, I would have cuffed him, put him in the car, I towed his motorcycle away and I took him to jail.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "reflected", "on", "this", "many", "times", "since", "Monday", ",", "and", "actually", ",", "if", "I", "had", "arrested", "him", ",", "I", "would", "have", "cuffed", "him", ",", "put", "him", "in", "the", "car", ",", "I", "towed", "his", "motorcycle", "away", "and", "I", "took", "him", "to", "jail", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Did you remember -- when this all came out on Monday, did you remember when you saw pictures of this man that you had had this encounter with him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "remember", "--", "when", "this", "all", "came", "out", "on", "Monday", ",", "did", "you", "remember", "when", "you", "saw", "pictures", "of", "this", "man", "that", "you", "had", "had", "this", "encounter", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, actually, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "That these girls had been found?", "question_tokens": ["That", "these", "girls", "had", "been", "found", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "I was at dinner with the family.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "at", "dinner", "with", "the", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Just on the Cleveland Police Department, and briefly if you don't mind, but do you feel there's any merit to the criticism that some people are leveling at the department, the fact that these three different missing girl cases all turned out to be at the same place, they had been tortured and raped and kidnapped and kept there for 10 years, do you believe that the police in any way dropped the ball in the investigation?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "on", "the", "Cleveland", "Police", "Department", ",", "and", "briefly", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", ",", "but", "do", "you", "feel", "there", "'s", "any", "merit", "to", "the", "criticism", "that", "some", "people", "are", "leveling", "at", "the", "department", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "these", "three", "different", "missing", "girl", "cases", "all", "turned", "out", "to", "be", "at", "the", "same", "place", ",", "they", "had", "been", "tortured", "and", "raped", "and", "kidnapped", "and", "kept", "there", "for", "10", "years", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "the", "police", "in", "any", "way", "dropped", "the", "ball", "in", "the", "investigation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, the reality of life is everybody can do my job better than me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "reality", "of", "life", "is", "everybody", "can", "do", "my", "job", "better", "than", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Cleveland Police Department"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "How is Gina and how are the family?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "Gina", "and", "how", "are", "the", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "I have spoken to the family, I spoke to Nancy, her mom, today.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "spoken", "to", "the", "family", ",", "I", "spoke", "to", "Nancy", ",", "her", "mom", ",", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "I mean, did she look like she'd been through 10 years of absolute hell?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "did", "she", "look", "like", "she", "'d", "been", "through", "10", "years", "of", "absolute", "hell", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "SPARRA: She actually doesn't.", "answer_tokens": ["SPARRA", ":", "She", "actually", "does", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "I understand that one of the strange aspects about her time in captivity is she's forgotten how to speak Spanish, how to understand Spanish, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "understand", "that", "one", "of", "the", "strange", "aspects", "about", "her", "time", "in", "captivity", "is", "she", "'s", "forgotten", "how", "to", "speak", "Spanish", ",", "how", "to", "understand", "Spanish", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Yes, that is -- that's the case.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "is", "--", "that", "'s", "the", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "EX", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "How do they feel about that aspect of it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "they", "feel", "about", "that", "aspect", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, interesting, I did talk to Nancy about it, and some of the relatives, and they told me that he actually appeared at the vigils that they were at because she had nine of them, and he would just stand there like concerned along with everyone else, and they -- they were concerned.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "interesting", ",", "I", "did", "talk", "to", "Nancy", "about", "it", ",", "and", "some", "of", "the", "relatives", ",", "and", "they", "told", "me", "that", "he", "actually", "appeared", "at", "the", "vigils", "that", "they", "were", "at", "because", "she", "had", "nine", "of", "them", ",", "and", "he", "would", "just", "stand", "there", "like", "concerned", "along", "with", "everyone", "else", ",", "and", "they", "--", "they", "were", "concerned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Did you ever see the young child who was born to Amanda Berry?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "see", "the", "young", "child", "who", "was", "born", "to", "Amanda", "Berry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "I have not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda Berry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Daisy, if I may start with you, and to put in context the background between you and Ariel Castro, you lived in Cleveland from 1988 to 2005 and your late fiance, Roberto, was the leader of the band that he played in, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Daisy", ",", "if", "I", "may", "start", "with", "you", ",", "and", "to", "put", "in", "context", "the", "background", "between", "you", "and", "Ariel", "Castro", ",", "you", "lived", "in", "Cleveland", "from", "1988", "to", "2005", "and", "your", "late", "fiance", ",", "Roberto", ",", "was", "the", "leader", "of", "the", "band", "that", "he", "played", "in", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1988", "2005"], "PERSON": ["Ariel Castro", "Roberto"], "LOCATION": ["Cleveland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2002", "2003", "2004"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "What kind of man is he?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "man", "is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, I knew him through 2002, 2003, 2004, during this period.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "knew", "him", "through", "2002", ",", "2003", ",", "2004", ",", "during", "this", "period", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "How do you feel about what he was doing that seemed so harmless at the time, given what you now know he's been accused of doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "what", "he", "was", "doing", "that", "seemed", "so", "harmless", "at", "the", "time", ",", "given", "what", "you", "now", "know", "he", "'s", "been", "accused", "of", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Harmless at the time, but now, Monday night when I found out about this all, there's really no words to describe how I feel.", "answer_tokens": ["Harmless", "at", "the", "time", ",", "but", "now", ",", "Monday", "night", "when", "I", "found", "out", "about", "this", "all", ",", "there", "'s", "really", "no", "words", "to", "describe", "how", "I", "feel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "You would see him and he would say, how are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "see", "him", "and", "he", "would", "say", ",", "how", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Have you ever heard anything quite like this in all the time you've been investigating this kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "heard", "anything", "quite", "like", "this", "in", "all", "the", "time", "you", "'ve", "been", "investigating", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Unfortunately, yes, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Unfortunately", ",", "yes", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "But in terms of the scale of this one, where you have three young women independently kidnapped at different periods of time, all taken back to the same house and then kept for a decade in the most appalling depravity, it really propels Ariel Castro, if he's convicted of all the crimes that he has been charged with, as one of the great sexual predators and monsters of modern American times, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "scale", "of", "this", "one", ",", "where", "you", "have", "three", "young", "women", "independently", "kidnapped", "at", "different", "periods", "of", "time", ",", "all", "taken", "back", "to", "the", "same", "house", "and", "then", "kept", "for", "a", "decade", "in", "the", "most", "appalling", "depravity", ",", "it", "really", "propels", "Ariel", "Castro", ",", "if", "he", "'s", "convicted", "of", "all", "the", "crimes", "that", "he", "has", "been", "charged", "with", ",", "as", "one", "of", "the", "great", "sexual", "predators", "and", "monsters", "of", "modern", "American", "times", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I agree with you, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "with", "you", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "FBI"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Do you think they deserve some criticism, the police?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "they", "deserve", "some", "criticism", ",", "the", "police", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "YAN: Frankly, Piers, from what -- our own interaction with the police, both the local police and the FBI, that wasn't the case.", "answer_tokens": ["YAN", ":", "Frankly", ",", "Piers", ",", "from", "what", "--", "our", "own", "interaction", "with", "the", "police", ",", "both", "the", "local", "police", "and", "the", "FBI", ",", "that", "was", "n't", "the", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "What is he?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "There are many terms we could apply to him.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "many", "terms", "we", "could", "apply", "to", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "What do you make of that part of what he may be facing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "part", "of", "what", "he", "may", "be", "facing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "It would be a very stupid decision on the part of prosecutors.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "a", "very", "stupid", "decision", "on", "the", "part", "of", "prosecutors", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ohio"]}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CD", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "CC", "IN", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Gloria, what do you say?", "question_tokens": ["Gloria", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Absolutely, I disagree with Alan, respectfully, of course, because the Ohio statute -- and I have reviewed it, 2903.01, talks about no person shall purposely and with prior calculation and design cause the unlawful termination of a pregnancy.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "I", "disagree", "with", "Alan", ",", "respectfully", ",", "of", "course", ",", "because", "the", "Ohio", "statute", "--", "and", "I", "have", "reviewed", "it", ",", "2903.01", ",", "talks", "about", "no", "person", "shall", "purposely", "and", "with", "prior", "calculation", "and", "design", "cause", "the", "unlawful", "termination", "of", "a", "pregnancy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Would that be it?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "be", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, I mean, I don't know whether the prosecutors are going to even offer him a plea.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "whether", "the", "prosecutors", "are", "going", "to", "even", "offer", "him", "a", "plea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Why would it be delayed that long, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "it", "be", "delayed", "that", "long", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Well, you know, preparing for a death penalty case is very complex.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "preparing", "for", "a", "death", "penalty", "case", "is", "very", "complex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Let's just talk, first of all, about your reaction as a mother, as someone who has been involved in trying to stop this epidemic, is what it is, of trafficking in what's happened in Cleveland, because it seems so horrific, doesn't it, on every level?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "just", "talk", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "about", "your", "reaction", "as", "a", "mother", ",", "as", "someone", "who", "has", "been", "involved", "in", "trying", "to", "stop", "this", "epidemic", ",", "is", "what", "it", "is", ",", "of", "trafficking", "in", "what", "'s", "happened", "in", "Cleveland", ",", "because", "it", "seems", "so", "horrific", ",", "does", "n't", "it", ",", "on", "every", "level", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "You know, I have to tell you that the unfortunate part is that it's not -- you know, when you're part of this advocacy, unfortunately it's not something new.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "have", "to", "tell", "you", "that", "the", "unfortunate", "part", "is", "that", "it", "'s", "not", "--", "you", "know", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "part", "of", "this", "advocacy", ",", "unfortunately", "it", "'s", "not", "something", "new", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cleveland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "To the victims?", "question_tokens": ["To", "the", "victims", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "ORGAN: What do you say to your kids?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "your", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I'm a different type of mother, in the fact that I share harsh realities with my children.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "different", "type", "of", "mother", ",", "in", "the", "fact", "that", "I", "share", "harsh", "realities", "with", "my", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]